so hello everyone um thank you for being
here today welcome to my talk zucchin or
cucumbers or how to Benchmark embeddings
for similar image retrieval thanks to
your weekly grocery
shopping I'd like us to start with a
little game imagine that you're building
an image recommendation model your user
is looking at this wonderful vegetable
and your model generates item
recommendations that should be
relevant these are the top 10 results
you get are there many good raise your
hands if you think all of the items or
retrieval finds are
cumbus raise your hand if you think at
least half of them are
cumbus well the L is right half of those
are zucchinis and the only way to tell
it apart from me is the shiny plastic on
the
cumbus let's do another game and I'm
really sorry for that it's the last do
before lunch I hope you won't be too M
watered but our users now looking at
this nice Granny Smith apple and your
model suggests all of these results
raise your hand if you think all of them
are Apple
now do you think at least half of them
are
apples well again you're right we get
one nice top top right and a
little pum Grenade on the bottom right
but when am I talking to you at a Tech
conference about comparing apples and
oranges my name is Paul and I've been
coding pretty much since I was 18 I'm a
software engineer since 2016 at algolia
and I've been focusing on machine
learning applications for the last five
years I built ipis and tools at algolia
from Android UI libraries helping you
build good search interfaces on the
mobile to tooling about voice search so
that you can get speech to text on any
mobile platform into your search
interface both of these are open source
by the way I've also be building natural
language apis and recently I focused on
this image recommendation engine so that
if you like this bedroom we can
recommend other ones that you might like
to this is my last project looking
similar an image recommendation API
based on vector embeddings and nearest
neighbor retrieval to return items that
might match your users's interests
top left is a live example from a
customer cabinet Parts if you break a
part of your cabinet you don't throw it
all away you just get the replacement
handle but it's hard to put this into
words whereas I can tell when I see it
that the slightly flatter one I need is
actually the second case same for this
example from a Romanian decoration item
shop this is pretty fancy ostrich lamp
and I wouldn't know how to put that into
query words either but I can see how our
model picks up other animal lamps items
I didn't even know that category existed
but we find it up because image Vector
models are able to semantically embed a
representation and to recognize that
this is about lamps decorations and
animals a last example there this is a
American based mosaic's website and they
have many different kind of Mosaic desel
when you look at this one and ask our
model we'll find the few other visually
similar mosaics that have the same kind
of semantic content here flowery
decorations so now you know what looking
similar is and you can definitely check
it out this is a link to the Ducks but
let me show you a quick peek of how
looking similar
Works in a nutshell this is a vector
retrieval API but like John solitario
said yesterday all great vector-based
user experiences are hybrid
approaches so we start from the vectors
using an image model to transform
arbitrary sized images into fix length
vectors we then turn them into smart
hashes using a learn semantic hashing
representation to Hash the semantically
Clos items in the same space of the of
the space we
project once we do this we can retrieve
them using yakal navigable small word
representation to give you approximate
nearest Neighbors From the image that
you inputed and finally
like Simmon said yesterday in his talk
um having some kind of filtering based
on object level metadata allows you to
focus Vector retrieval results and
enable many different use
cases to me this works really well we're
solving here the call start problem when
you want to have recommendations on data
while you still don't have any kind of
user interactions to build collabora
filtering matrices on top of so this
works great and we are starting to
onboard d divers kinds of customers in
many different
verticals and one day one customer C me
by surprise with a
question do you handle groceries well
how would I know do I look like I have
groceries in my
home this is a good question do we know
how to recognize food with this model if
you watch the show Silicon Valley you
know that there are state-of-the-art
Technologies to recognize food or not
food so clear
we need to step up our game and to prove
that we can do at least as good as that
and at this point I was pretty confident
it would be a day of work I could just I
just need a benchmark so that I can
compare our model on the existing
data so I started searching for a
benchmark and uh I was a bit surprised I
was assuming surely if don't have if I
don't have groceries in my kitchen
someone else's has so there must be
industry standards for testing food
image
recognition one industry standard data
set for images is image net lots of
images lots of classes and many of them
are about food that's that looks like it
could work out and when I looked at the
imag the data itself there's nice more
or less user generated pictures of food
I can work with
that but then I realized there is a
problem with using this data set I had
the expectation that any IM model can be
tested on any image data set and
Benchmark I would expect something very
tidy and organized like cable management
at a data
center the reality is that these
industry benchmarks are already used in
training in testing in validation of
those models and so you'll be based in
many surprising ways if you take this as
gospel it looks more like cable
management at my home if you
will indeed when looking at the image
model that we're using which is rest net
vectors it has been trained using image
net data so if I'm trying to assess its
performance on its training data I will
have a very high metric that's also
meaningless it's a self-fulfilling
prophecy and it's dangerous to take this
as
truth but what about other image models
you you probably heard about clip the
open AI joint text image embedding model
that has been very successful made a lot
of noise when released and we have many
people integrating it in their to Tool
chains such as our friends at pinec con
so maybe I can test clip an image net
data when I looked into the paper and
the research page I noticed that clip is
heavily assessed on image net you'll see
on the right here 35 mentions of image
net in the clip research page so it's
not used as training data but you could
say it has been definitely tested and
iterated on until it had good metrics on
reset on imet you might say that uh it
has been gamed against this data set and
so it's not something that I can use and
Trust for building my own evaluation of
the image recommendation
engine so if there is no available
Benchmark can I create one what would it
take what what is a
benchmark this was the first Challenge
on my journey I cannot find any good
Benchmark for this use case but our
customers still need an answer so the
one afternoon task turned into a Sprint
long
challenge because if it's hard to find a
good Benchmark there are definitely data
sets lying around can I leverage these I
found the data set in the paper a
multi-layer hierarchy of natural user
generated images by Classon and all and
this looks good to me there's like 5,000
images of of food items taken in a
grocery shopping ALS across 40 different
categories 80 different uh single key
items clearly this would give me an idea
of the performance of our model for this
customer use
case but as you can see it's not very
structured it is a data a folder with
threey with images can I turn a threey
of data points into labelled
examples there were a few metadata with
those images but it's mostly lowly
structured text description and some
information I was a bit disappointed I
was expecting CSV or Json data not this
so I started structuring the data I
started writing code and there is a good
practice in code which is you ain't
going to need it don't add things that
you're not sure will be
useful in this case what do I do with
the description and
information I would argue when you're
building a benchmark you should not
follow yagy you should rather follow
what I called immani you might also need
it keep all the data at hand because the
Benchmark you build today for a given
use case which is here image image to
image recommendation grocery evaluation
might very well serve other peoples on
your team when they're building new
features so how do we go structuring
this data I would call it a kind of
magic which is just good old Cod I
turned the Tria key traversing these
transforming each item into a structured
record so that the end result would be
something more like this
which allows me to take each individual
item and assess it against different
properties this is the first Insight I
got when working on this project that
labels in a data set are a kind of Groom
tools hence you can turn them into a
metric does this mean then that all I
have to do is to write tests for these
labels on my data I'm an engineer I can
write test this was really the key
Insight I found when answering this
question
any label data set is a benchmark we're
asking you to be
built really this is the only ID if you
remember one thing from this talk you
should remember this a benchmark is only
a data set with testable
labels in our case building The
Benchmark means just turning the labels
of the original data set into things
that we can test to compute metrics over
a runoff or model on this data set this
makes it possible for your development
practice to be data driven from the data
at hand Define objectives measure them
and iterate from
there with that in mind we now have two
steps to work structuring the data set
and evaluating our
algorithm so the structuring I will
simply iterate on each of the splits in
the data set I'm not training a model I
can keep all of the data and I will uh
browse this data set to create records
save these objects in a data store here
I used algolia index because it's the
simplest tool I know to store lowly
structured data and make quick sense of
it you can store up to a million items
in there without putting a credit card
that's good for
me and once I had this uh process of
going through the data set and creating
my structured I could then Define those
records based on the properties that I
had identified for each of the item
storing that this is a granny smith
apple so that it is in the Granny Smith
subcategory that it is in the Apple
category and that ultimately the top
category is a
fruit and again a good practice here you
see I'm adding all of the metadata that
was listed in the files because you
might well need it so let's keep this
textual information and don't erase
labels just because you don't need them
for
now you might also need
it now we have some data in a data store
that we can run the model on we can
start evaluating our model
but what do we want to
measure the real the real question is
what do we want to know about our
algorithm here we have a customer
question about the quality of results
for groceries so we want to evaluate the
quality of those recommendations but
what does this really mean for a user it
boils down to the problem you're trying
to solve here the customer's request was
to find the right
groceries so they're interested in
Precision rather than recall you want
for an apple to have only apples and
know how hot
dogs they're not really interested in
the recall having all of the apples in
your top five recommendations is less of
a concern for the customer what they
care about is having mostly
apples but they also care about having
something to show you heard the dreaded
no result screen being mentioned a few
time already at hastac so indeed always
having something and having a low no
results rate is of interest for this
customer then we have our metrics we
want to check that we got results that
for each item it's in the same category
same subcategory ideally even the same
product SKU that the input item that our
model will look
at so I turn these into evaluation
criteria what you're looking at is the
bench. P script I built which for each
item in the data set defines a query to
our recommendation API I will get the
recommendations for this query and I
will just look at the hits that we
return if we have some I can check the
quality
against the Matrix that we Define and if
we have nothing I will just not that
down to compute a no match rate that
will help us see how many of the items
might get no
recommendations I then print overall
metrics on the data set this is just a
cheap trick for your development speed
so that you can quickly look and iterate
without having to put it in the
dashboard and the evaluation step itself
is really just comparing the labels is
the category of the recommended item the
same as the original one is the
subcategory the same is even the item
SKU the same one the first half of this
code is just evaluating my Matrix but
you might notice a few what the f at the
bottom of the code this is because I
noticed in the data set that sometimes I
would have items that have the same
subcategory but not the same category I
think the actual case was a mushroom
that was in a vegetable but another kind
of mushroom that was in fruits
if you have any assumptions in your
metrics I was assuming that the same
category is an easier test than the same
subcategory write those assumptions down
and test them during The Benchmark you
got to be careful that it could be a
garbage in garbage out case where if you
have inconsistencies in the data set you
will have inconsistencies in your
benchmark metrix and if you notice them
after running the only sound scientific
conclusion is that you should throw away
the previous measurements and I hate it
so it's worth a double check before you
communicate your results outside the
lab another tip I would give you when
running these benchmarks in a regular
way is to make it reliable you don't
want the Benchmark to be run the next
day and to look totally different from
what it was the same input same model
same data points should result in the
same scores for the same metrics so
depending on the system you will be
testing you want to make sure that you
get uh consistent results you want to
have Frozen any large language model you
use so that updates won't change your
model's
performance you want to use random seed
if there is any kind of Randomness in
the tools you use if you have
collaborative filtering matrices that
are initialized at random make sure you
initialize them at the same random every
time you run the
Benchmark and this generalizes if you
have any source of Randomness in your
system eliminate it or at least freeze
it so that you can have consistent
metrics and assess your system week over
week as it
evolves so now we have data and labels
the next step in our adventure is to
evaluate
something and once I have this scripts
running them is actually quite easy here
you're looking at an experiment we did
replacing rest net vectors by clip we'll
run them locally generate Json
predictions and I can load them in the
Benchmark and have a nice uh evaluation
of the impact of changing the
embeddings I was expecting a huge impact
there clip is so popular we can expect
big improvements over res net like we
saw in the
paper here I'm sharing with you some
results for the reset uh Baseline and
indeed if we get back to the clip paper
on every category of confusing images
they have significant improvements so if
I didn't have the Benchmark I would say
let's just use clip but I have a
benchmark so I can look at actual
results I am glad that there was one
line with the same value because
otherwise you would just se you would
just think I have put a red column and a
green column I I trust me these are
conditional formatting line by line
excruciating to write in Google Sheets
and the result is that it's just readed
every time in the Baseline on the reset
embeddings and green every time in clip
I'm an engineer when I look at that I
get excited I just want to throw away
rest net and use clip it's good to wait
a little and to graph those metrics
because it's not that obvious that clip
is better when you actually look at the
significance of the difference some of
these were non significant actually
worse in our testing right now our
production scales indexing to a million
items in 24 hours predictions including
because we can index with eight parallel
threads when using rest net embeddings
in our testing with clip we had to scale
that down to two parallel threads to
avoid having instability and reest
timeouts on the clip embeddings I am not
saying this is the clip problem it's
probably our engineering team and myself
which haven't cracked yet how to use it
but as a pragmatic engineer this to me
means it's not ready for production I
don't see a clear-cut argument for
putting engineering effort into
replacing a vector and Bing by another
when the difference on this Benchmark is
is not so
big this to me was insightful because it
shows we humans have and even experts
can have wrong assumptions about how a
system
behaves let's see if evaluating this
Benchmark can teach us more
learnings I'm going to share you a few
concrete results because again I had
expectations on the strength and
weaknesses of image
recommendations for example package
Goods I would have shown that packaged
goods are hard to recognize this book of
uh soyt looks like a box of milk or a
box of anything to me the reality is
that there is so much signal in the
labeling that it's very easy for the
model to pick it up I was surprised to
see that not only we only have alpro
product we only have alpro vanilla soyt
product for the first eight results and
then we generalize to the non vanilla
but blueberry Flav
world it's way easier to differentiate
than let's say a TV and an oven you
might be surprised by this example I
surely were surely was when I saw a
customer telling us when looking at a TV
it recommends an
oven when you look at the data it is
maybe not so different from a uh image
recognition model perspective it's not
so different when you look at the
product chart focused but when you look
at the items in context as they suggest
you to use it in your house I can
understand why the model is confused if
you're putting TVs in your
kitchen so on the other hand you know
the idiom about comparing apples and
oranges I had a very strong assumption
that fruits are different and that the
skin of an orange is totally different
from the skin of an apple enter Pink
Ladies which is a kind of oranges Apple
when I look at the recommendations on
The Benchmark well I get mostly apples
but I also get two oranges in the top 20
recommendations and I'm not even
mentioning peaches and pomegranates on
the way so fruits are not that different
from a machine learning model train on
imag classes
perspective this was the core point of
using a benchmark your AI models
strength and weaknesses are not what we
humans think they
are which brings the question know that
we have a better understanding of our
model how can we share the learnings
from this benchmark
you got to remember why we are doing
this the goal here is not to get numbers
at whatever it's to answer a customer
question what is the problem you are
trying to solve with these measurements
if you understand the need you can
understand the right Framing and the
level of details that you should
communicate results
with and to understand the need we need
to understand who we're talking
to do we just share category Precision
at 1 equals
99.2 this is the truth but it's a bit
meaningless to a nontechnical
person and sharing these RW results
might do more harm than good on the
perception of your product or of your
engineering
team we're talking to humans not
machines so let's phrase this in human
terms the top recommendation is in the
same category as the source item for
99.6% of your prod of all
pictures because ultimately your
interlocutors are not interested in
metrics they want a quantitative
assessment of the usefulness of a
product they want to know if they can
trust your API with your with their use
case and so if what they want is a
quantitative assessment of the
usefulness of a product you should focus
on making the report actionable what do
you expect your readers to do just after
they finish reading your
report how can you optimize for
Action this depends what you want to say
about our algorithm here we could share
the Precision we we want to share a
metric that's tied to the customer value
you could report Precision at one it's
very good-looking also pretty useless in
the context of a recommendation UI if
you look at Precision at three this is
the main customer use case on a search
result page on a landing page on a
product page in your cart they will
display three maybe five recommendations
and those need to be spot
on but if you want to look at the Hard
truth Precision at 30 the whole set of
results is the bottom line out of all
the images we retrieve for these apples
how many are any
good all three are valuable I would say
it just depends what you want to
communicate and to
whom I was happy at this point I know
have results I can write emails I can
write an email to the customer replying
to the question and a message to my Dev
colleagues to iterate on the model and a
report to my product manager so that
they understand what are our current
strength and what are our current weak
points in three cases I I would argue
you want to optimize for Action so the
data is the same but the goals of your
interlocutors are different and hence
the message
changes to my Dev colleagues I might
well say the same product at tree is
around 88.6 and I think we should try
these few things to to see if we can
improve the
metric to our product manager I want to
focus on where we are good in our
carusel UI components which is the main
use case for this API we can expect that
80% of the top three results will be the
same single key identifier as the user
input and finally for our customers we
want to tell them the bottom line that
they can be confident that on most
groceries in their catalog the top
recommendations will be relevant
these are three examples of messages but
you might have different interlocutors
so I think we should think about this
with interlocutor
personas first of all you have Technical
and non-technical people you communicate
with and you want to serve
both for the technical audiences uh they
want to know how to run the Benchmark
they would love to adapt it to new
features and they're curious what can be
improved in our model so make share
Hands-On knowledge
make it modular so that people can reuse
The Benchmark with Hands-On guidance on
how to run it also mention every
limitation you encountered in The
Benchmark but also about the model I now
know that we have weak points on apples
and
oranges on the other hand when you're
talking to non-technical audiences you
would drone them with irrelevant details
if you took the same
messaging they're not interested in how
to run it they want to know how to
Leverage The Benchmark they need aable
talking points especially your
colleagues in customer facing roles like
sales and marketing they want to know
what they can say about the model not
how to run a benchmark they must know
the core
strength so you want to make the report
self- serve Define every term explain
precision and recall in layman terms
that make sense for your
interlocutors you want to give
ammunition to the customer facing roles
show them where it really works show the
use cases where the feature shines maybe
share some good demos that they can run
in their own calls and mention the use
cases that have best avoided for now I
think as product Builders we need to be
humble to say what works but also to
State what doesn't to avoid wrong
expectations about what our features
are this is about Technical and
non-technical interlocutors but you
might also want to make a difference
between the internal and the external
audiences of your reports
when you're talking to your internal
colleagues you want to make them
understand the strength and the
weaknesses in a crude light to know what
they can improve and what to focus on so
I would argue you should focus on the
edge cases where do we fail that looks
good to that looks weird to you can we
improve those edge cases with different
setups without lowering the bar so have
an exhaustive report focus on those edge
cases and share ideas how you think the
feature can be improved it might just be
far in the road map but note them down
as you have them building a benchmark
gives you insights it would be too bad
to lose
them on the other hand when talking
about external audiences you want to be
honest but you maybe don't want to focus
on the weak points you would rather want
to show what your cases are solid where
people can trust your system today as of
now with their use
cases you want to Ace those core use
cases having great documentation
Hands-On guides demos if you can so that
really what you identified as a core
strength is leveraged for your product
and for your
business when it's not a strong use case
but you see ways to make it work share
the work around we had examples with our
image recommendation API where if you're
looking at clothing and you have a very
uh slight clothing and visible muscles
it would give you other shots that are
also muscles and if you're looking at a
top where your arm is flexed we might
recommend you bottoms with a flexed leg
in that case filtering with categories
is something that would allow you to
refine and limit a lot uh the results
that you get to something more
relevant but some H cases are simply not
well handled in this case don't try to
fit a square into a round you should
rather focus on alternative features
that are better suited to this case and
like Trey mentioned in the talk just
before you might want to do rather
content based embeddings looking at the
description of the product the titles
Etc maybe these are better than average
images so now we know where our model is
strong and where it isn't we're back
we're back to our model here we go again
we have a Baseline and we can iterate on
it because product development is a
never-ending process in a good way I
would argue it is a nice feedback loop
where you build something you test it
you communicate results and you get back
to business
building so what did we learn about our
models with this Benchmark first of all
the good news is that we support grocery
shopping pretty well so the customer
that asked us can go ahead and build
value on top of our model do you
remember the zucchini and cumbus example
I showed you earlier I had to Cherry
peek the hell out of it to find an
example that had pretty average results
most of the zucchin will mostly get
zucchinis
and same for apples actually this pink
lady was really a trickster because most
of the apples you see don't look like
oranges and if you put a granny smith in
you might have some Golden Delicious out
but you mostly get
apples I still saw some edge cases on
these examples remember the four metrics
that we had defined if we look at them
for those two kind of sets of results
The Matrix at tree don't look so good on
the Granny Smith we get some
we get the same fruit category we get
mostly the Apple subcategory but none of
them are Golden Delicious that doesn't
look good likewise on the bottom when I
have a shot of a zucchini that also
includes a bottom row with some bell
paper the model is confused and the
results are green band paper with also
yellow ones on the side and you might
already have ideas how to improve
that one option we considered as you saw
with clip is to use a different
eding we could simply change the vector
model that is at the beginning of our
system Pipeline and see if it improves
likely it will improve results on food
item and
groceries but I would be wary of taking
just this one Benchmark as a reason to
change the whole embedding we are now
very confident how it works on the food
items and maybe we should try another
embedding that we have better metrics
there but not all your users are doing
grocery shopping and maybe someone doing
a Futurama character matching will
suddenly get hot dogs out probably this
is not what you want the Benchmark tells
you one view into your system but like
the philosopher volter said reading a
single Journal is watching the word
through a single hole I would say the
same for benchmarks running a single
Benchmark is a risk of seeing your
system with a single
perspective so we can try all things
before changing the image ble itself
when you saw the example with zucchin
one of the issue was that the image is
not focused we also have something else
in it so we could try alternative models
we could try image preprocessing to
Simply refine the images there's
techniques from basic image manipulation
better contrast saturation Etc two more
opinionated ones like mixing image paper
where you just Blend images together and
send the overall vectors to your
system we can also try adding object
segmentation if we focus on the zucchini
we likely have better results as well
and avoid those bell
peppers we can try many things adding
textual signals in the vectors embedding
the metadata using joint embedding like
clip allows that and those are just a
few ideas you can get creative this is
the whole point of having a benchmark
that you can run daily for cheap you
cannot afford to experiment as much as
you'd
like and you can do it too I would say
no this is your turn what kind of
customer's problem is your system
solving do you already have data that
describes good and bad
outcomes if if you don't have no threat
can you find a data set that is close to
the use case you're trying to
solve when you'll have the data think
what success looks like to you can you
describe what you would like to measure
as success this is your metric for
example if you care about having always
something to show you can measure the no
result rate at K and try to have it as
low as
possible if you care about never showing
Apple products to someone looking at a
Samsung tablet probably what you want is
a category spread at k um where the
percentage of items in the category a
with recommendations from category B and
vice versa should be as low as
possible and SC is the limit you can
care about very complex scenarios when
you're assessing a use case maybe you
want to optimize for the top category
xx6 while keeping the average quality
under control I would say then you need
two metrics one which is the top
category recall and you want it as high
as possible while keeping the category
Precision above a quality sailing that
you think is the bare minimal to have
good General
results honestly a metric is right as
long as it captures the value you build
and you're the expert in what you're
building in and how it is valuable so
you can get creative in the metric
Define because this is the best way for
you to assess the quality of your
models so I want to leave you with this
conclusion you can build a benchmark a
hacky Benchmark is better than nothing
we know have a way limited but way
better understanding of the quality of
our
system and we didn't have data at hands
but the first data set we found was a
good match I would say that any data is
better than
none thank you
[Applause]
thank you do we have
questions yeah I was wondering um if I
mean to maybe take your idea with the
the groceries Benchmark um is the kind
of just the whole idea what you're
saying is you can also do that for
different types of benchmarks so if if
another customer asks you for like you
know you know a DIY store and they want
to know if you can figure the you know
that out then you're like okay I'll go
build a benchmark in the same way that I
did for the groceries is that like
you're what you're saying yes I think
that's the idea uh right now we have one
Benchmark but I'm looking forward to
more customers question that's going to
allow us to deepen this I think in the
long run even without customer demands
we might want to invest in that
ourselves just to have internal
visibility on our system uh the more the
less control you have over a system and
you so this is quite a pipeline we have
the vector embeddings we have the learn
hashing we have the hierarchical
representation things can go wrong at
every step so if you are trying to build
an API that serves diverse customer use
cases in different verticals I think
every important vertical for you should
be one that you can quantitatively
access like
this any other questions
yeah uh yes uh thanks for the for the
talk it was very interesting you me you
mentioned zero
results and it looks like
um this approach can return zero results
and it's kind of surprising because
usually Vector search always returns the
Z because you has some nearest neighbor
somewhere so how how come okay this is
an excellent question uh it it get back
to the talk by isan on prefix box that
says if you build pure Vector results
it's not a great user experience because
there will always be something even if
it's a bad one so here our approach was
to have a default quality threshold that
if the vector's similarity is too low
we'll just eliminate that you can still
control the threshold with your IPI so
if you want to get all the results feel
free but what we one thing also is that
we're not really focusing on building uh
state-of-the-art models but really on
building useful products that will
create good user experiences and no
result uh page is an interesting case
because a no results page doesn't mean
you have nothing to show in a case where
you have no results well sure you could
show the the F the closest neighbor that
might be a bad a bad Vector but I would
argue you should rather show a default
state that guides your users back into a
happy path Maybe by showing popular
queries Maybe by using Trend models to
show what are trending images and
products in the catalog there are many
ways you can create a good uxix to
recover from an results page and so what
we recommend to our customers is to
consider their no result experience not
necessarily as a failure but sometimes
as an opportunity to guide the users
towards your top selling items towards
the interesting queries towards your new
recommendations so depending on the use
case you build sometime no results is
something you
want okay I I I have another question
just a quick one so
um it's I mean it's a question about the
use case uh why vegetables why groceries
it's not the first use case that we can
think of I I I see very well the use
case where you have like very specific
items like you shown the the the lamp or
the things like that where what that you
cannot describe easily and that you they
that might might not even have a name so
they just you know it looks like that
and that's all um but for vegetables
it's something like I mean they have a
name it's very easy to search them by by
keywords and especially the baskets are
like uh 30 40 products and you don't
even have time to make photos of the
items that you want to search so yeah
yes that's a good question that use case
I agree that it's a it's not the first
use case you would think of when
thinking image recommendations I am not
exactly sure of what that customers
business was but if I recall correctly
there are two cases where we see image
recommendations as a good first step one
of them is the cot problem when you
don't have user interactions and you
still want to show some recommendations
you need to make them content based I
agree using the title and description
can be a good fit however the second
kind of customers we s that are begging
for image models are those who have more
or less qualitative textual data the
example like the typical example for
that is a B2B or customer to customer
marketplaces which will be selling
random listings changed every day with
more or less structured Tex sometime in
different languages and I think there
are I think that customer had a catalog
with many many different groceries that
were more or less named differently
moving away from the food examples
especially as we're all getting hungry
uh I've been also looking at a at a
sport uh vertically integrated seller
who designed their own cloes and sold
them cloes online and the issue they
have is they quickly add new things new
IDs on their catalog a designer drone
design they will create a 100 or 300
items and see if it sells and so the
pipeline for adding new items sometime
drops a few metadata on the way you will
add an item and maybe it is a woman
leggings but categorized in men leggings
or maybe it is a short but it was called
differently so having a way to leverage
images as a source of of Truth is
valuable when the Tex data has in
Direction and in the case of food maybe
it's called a pink lady or a granny
smith I can see it I can tell it when I
see it it's an
apple let's thank our
[Applause]
speaker as has been
mention e